let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Artificial Intelligence is about_____?",
        answer: "Making a machine Intelligent",
        options: [
            "Playing a game on Computer",
            "Making a machine Intelligent",
            "Programming on Machine with your Own Intelligence",
            "Putting your intelligence in Machine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who is known as the -Father of AI?",
        answer: " John McCarthy",
        options: [
            "Fisher Ada",
            "Alan Turing",
            "John McCarthy",
            "Allen Newell"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Select the most appropriate situation for that a blind search can be used?",
        answer: "Small Search Space",
        options: [
            "Real-life situation",
            "Small Search Space",
            "Complex game",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The application/applications of Artificial Intelligence is/are?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "Expert Systems",
            "Gaming",
            "Vision Systems",
            "All of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Among the given options, which search algorithm requires less memory?",
        answer: "Depth First Search",
        options: [
            "Optimal Search",
            "Depth First Search",
            "Breadth-First Search",
            "Linear Search"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "If a robot is able to change its own trajectory as per the external conditions, then the robot is considered as the__?",
        answer: "Intelligent",
        options: [
            "Mobile",
            "Non-Servo",
            "Open Loop",
            "Intelligent"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
        answer: "Perl",
        options: [
            "LISP",
            "PROLOG",
            "Python",
            "Perl"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "A technique that was developed to determine whether a machine could or could not demonstrate the artificial intelligence known as the___?",
        answer: "Turing Test",
        options: [
            "Boolean Algebra",
            "Turing Test",
            "Logarithm",
            "Algorithm"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The component of an Expert system is_________?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "Knowledge Base",
            "Inference Engine",
            "User Interface",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " Which algorithm is used in the Game tree to make decisions of Win/Lose?",
        answer: "Min/Max Algorithm ",
        options: [
            "Heuristic Search Algorithm",
            "DFS/BFS algorithm",
            "Greedy Search Algorithm",
            "Min/Max algorithm"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "The available ways to solve a problem of state-space-search?",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: " Among the given options, which is not the required property of Knowledge representation?",
        answer: " Representational Verification",
        options: [
            "Inferential Efficiency",
            "Inferential Adequacy",
            "Representational Verification",
            "Representational Adequacy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "An AI agent perceives and acts upon the environment using___?",
        answer: " Both a and c",
        options: [
            "Sensors",
            "Perceiver",
            "Actuators",
            "Both a and c"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which rule is applied for the Simple reflex agent?",
        answer: "Condition-action rule",
        options: [
            "Simple-action rule",
            "Simple &Condition-action rule",
            "Condition-action rule",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Which agent deals with the happy and unhappy state?",
        answer: " Utility-based agent",
        options: [
            "Utility-based agent",
            "Model-based agent",
            "Goal-based Agent",
            "Learning Agent"
        ]
    },
];